<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IllumiSmart</string>
    <string name="illumismart">IllumiSmart</string>
    <string name="self_assessment">Self-Assessment</string>
    <string name="home_selfassess">Evaluate the lighting condition of your workplace by answering a few questions.</string>
    <string name="measure_light_level">Measure Light Level</string>
    <string name="home_lightlevel">A quick tool to check whether your working area is too bright or too dark.</string>
    <string name="home_flicker">A quick tool to check whether there is flicker hazard.</string>
    <string name="detect_light_flicker">Detect Light Flicker</string>
    <string name="detect_glare">Detect Glare</string>z
    <string name="glare_event_true">Glare Detected</string>
    <string name="glare_event_false">No Glare Detected</string>
    <string name="self_assessment_extra_name">self assessment extra name</string>
    <string name="a_quick_tool_to_check_whether_there_is_glare_hazard">A quick tool to check whether there is glare hazard.</string>
    <string name="lightlevel_guidance">Light level is an important factor in the workplace. To measure the illuminance using this function:\n\n
        1. Push \t\t\t to start recording \n
        2. Face the light sensor up \n
        3. Moving the phone horizontally and slowly around the working area \n
        4. Push \t\t\t to pause recording \n\n
        In addition:\n
        \t\t : Reset the light meter \n
        \t\t : Save the measurement data</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance">Unsteady light may do harm to human and become safety hazards. To detect the possible flicker using this function: \n\n
        1. Face the light sensor direct to the light source \n
        2. Push \t\t\t to start detecting \n
        3. The Fluctuation Rate of the light source and whether it is a possible visible flicker will be displayed after 10 seconds \n\n
        In addition:\n
        \t\t : Reset the detector \n
        \t\t : Save the measurement data</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance_0">No flicker event detected.</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance_1to3">It seems this light source is a possible flicker.</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance_3">It seems this light source is a certain visible flicker.</string>
    <string name="light_level_guidance_below">The average lighting level is below the guideline suggestions.</string>
    <string name="light_level_guidance_above">The average lighting level is above the guideline suggestions</string>
    <string name="light_level_guidance_among">The average lighting level follows the guidance.</string>
    <string name="light_level_view_details"><u>View Details</u></string>
    <string name="profile_below40_finework">According to your age and type of task being done, the recommended illuminance is:</string>
    <string name="light_level_below_suggest">If the measured average light level is under the guidance, view</string>
    <string name="light_level_below_suggest_correct"><u>Correction of Insufficient Light</u></string>
    <string name="light_level_above_suggest">If the measured average light level is above the guidance, it is suggested to conduct a glare test next.</string>
    <string name="occupation_question">Which of the following answers best describes your work type?</string>
    <string name="occupation_general_txt">Examples: Storeroom…</string>
    <string name="occupation_moderate_txt">Examples: Packing; despatch…</string>
    <string name="occupation_precise_txt">Examples: Simple assembly; locksmith’s work; winding thick wire onto spools; work on carpenter’s bench; milling…</string>
    <string name="occupation_fine_txt">Examples: Reading; writing; book-keeping; laboratory technician; assembly of fine equipment; woodworking by machine; fine work on toolmaking gig…</string>
    <string name="occupation_veryfine_txt">Examples: Technical drawing; colour proofing; adjusting and testing electrical equipement; assembling delicate electronics; watchmaking; invisible mending</string>
    <string name="age_question">What is your age?</string>
    <string name="question1_work">Do you work in the office or industry setting?</string>
    <string name="question_select_header">Choose one of the following</string>
    <string name="question2_discomfort">Are there any signs of frequent eye discomfort (e.g. eyestrain, blurred vision…) and/or headaches?</string>
    <string name="question_back_header">Back to the Previous Question</string>
    <string name="question3_sunlight">Does your workplace have access to the natural light (sunlight) via windows?</string>
    <string name="question4_curtains">Are there blinds or curtains on windows?</string>
    <string name="question5_computer">Do you have a computer in your working area and usually work with it?</string>
    <string name="question6_monitor_position">Which of the following answers best describes your desktop monitor position relative to the windows?</string>
    <string name="question6_a">Next to a window</string>
    <string name="question6_b">In front of a window</string>
    <string name="question6_c">Face to a window</string>
    <string name="question6_d">There is no window near my monitor</string>
    <string name="question7_paper">Do you sometimes feel it is difficult to view the paper documents on the desk?</string>
    <string name="question8_vision">Are there frequent transitions of vision between extremes of light and dark or near and far during working?</string>
    <string name="question9_lightbulb">When do you replace the light bulbs?</string>
    <string name="question9_a">When they stop working</string>
    <string name="question9_b">When the light is dimming or fluctuating</string>
    <string name="question9_c">On regular schedule</string>
    <string name="question10_clean">Do you usually clean light fixtures, upper walls, ceilings and task stations?</string>
    <string name="question10_a">Yes, on regular schedule or whenever needed</string>
    <string name="question10_b">Never</string>
    <string name="question1suggest">
        Sorry, this assessment is temporarily for office workers only. Newer versions of assessment for industry settings will be updated in the future :)
    </string>
    <string name="question2suggest_a">
        In general, eye discomfort symptoms may be caused by: \n
        1. poor lighting \n
        2. glare on a computer or tablet screen \n
        3. poor quality computer or tablet screen (e.g., poor resolution, blurry image, etc.)\n
        4. improper viewing distances \n
        5. poor sitting posture \n
        6. uncorrected vision problems \n
        7. dry air \n
        8. air movement, or \n
        9. a combination of these factors \n\n
        Other examples of work-related risk factors that contribute to eye discomfort are: \n
        1. maintaining a fixed and close visual distance for a long time, \n
        2. glare from the unshaded or un-diffused lighting fixtures, \n
        3. poor lighting, involving unchanged (and unchangeable) levels of illumination,\n
        4. unsuitable workstations (dimensions and arrangement),\n
        5. low ambient humidity,\n
        6. uncorrected vision problems, and \n
        7. lack of colour variety in one\'s surroundings.\n\n
        As you go through this assessment, some of the problems above will be addressed. If the eye discomfort has not been reduced after suggested actions taken, have your eyes examined by an eye specialist or medical professional.
    </string>
    <string name="question4suggest_b">
        It is recommended to have blinds or curtains on your windows, as they can control the amount of daylight entering the workplace. Excessive amounts of daylight may cause annoying reflections, and some angles of light may cause glares. It is important to adjust the curtains positions accordingly.
    </string>
    <string name="question6suggest_b">
        Placing your monitor in front of the window is not a wise choice. When looking at the monitor, the daylight coming through the window can be a source of glare and make it difficult to see the contents on the screen. To confirm, put your hands on the top of the monitor to shield some light entering the window. If such a shield makes the contents on the screen more visible, then the glare is presented.\n\n
        As a means of eliminating window-related glare, it is suggested that you place your screen at a ninety-degree angle from all nearby windows, or else that you make use of window shades.
    </string>
    <string name="question6suggest_c">
        Facing the monitor to a window is not a wise choice. The monitor is a reflective surface and will reflect the external light source and possibly cause glare. The presence of glare is easily determined by turning off your screen. If glare is present, you will obviously see it all over your darkened screen.\n\n
        As a means of eliminating window-related glare, it is suggested that you place your screen at a ninety-degree angle from all nearby windows, or else that you make use of window shades. If you\’ve already taken all possible steps to handle the glare and find it still present, then perhaps a third-party accessory is needed. Glare and light filters are often used for this purpose.
    </string>
    <string name="question7suggest_a">
        Difficulty of seeing is usually due to insufficient light or high contrast in the visual environment. Most office work involves using the monitor and paper documents at the same time. Paper documents require a higher light level than the monitor. Glare can result from an improper match or excessive contrast in light levels between the monitor screen and the paper.\n\n
        To address this, first, check whether the documents are placed in the shadows. If so, move it away from the shadows or remove the objects that caused the shadows. If there is still insufficient light, a desk lamp (any type of soft task light) can be used to illuminate documents while avoiding excessive light near the monitor.
    </string>
    <string name="question8suggest_a">
        The pupil and the retina of the eye can cope with changes in luminance only after a certain delay so that fluctuating brightness leaves the eyes either under- or over-exposed for much of the time. It is suggested that all the objects and major surfaces along the main axes of sight should appear to be about equally bright, and it is better to place the task objects as near as possible to avoid exhaustedly moving the sight.
    </string>
    <string name="question9suggest_a">
        Replacing a light bulb when it does not work is always the easiest way. However, it is also important to notice that sometimes even if the light bulb is working, it may still need to be replaced due to dimming or flickering. Using the "Light Level Measurement" function to test if the light bulb is less bright, and using the "Flicker Detection" function to check whether it is flickering. Troubleshoot and replace the light bulbs when necessary.\n\n
        Tip: Replacing your incandescents and halogen bulbs with LEDs will save you money in the long run. The money you spend to power a 60-Watt incandescent bulb for the maximum 2,000-hour lifespan could pay the initial cost of purchasing an energy-saving LED.
    </string>
    <string name="question9suggest_b">
        It seems you have a great sense of taking care of your eyes! Just note that, not just the light bulb itself, many other factors such as power fluctuations, corrupt or incorrect wiring may cause the light unstable. Before replacing the light bulbs, you may troubleshoot them by the tips given in this article: https://blog.1000bulbs.com/home/help-my-lights-dont-work.
    </string>
    <string name="question9suggest_c">
        It seems you have a great sense of taking care of your lamps! The following table lists the accepted average life hours of different standard types of light bulbs, which may help you better adjust your replacing schedule.
    </string>
    <string name="question10suggest_b">
        To reach proper light levels and uniform light distribution in the visual environment, many light fixtures are designed to reflect light off walls, ceilings and objects.  Components of the light fixtures such as the covers are crucial for light to be diffused evenly, and dirt on walls or ceilings may influence the surface reflectance. It is recommended to clean light fixtures, upper walls, ceilings and task stations regularly to avoid poorly distributed light.
    </string>
    <string name="question2suggest_a_keyword">
        Eye Discomfort
    </string>
    <string name="question4suggest_b_keyword">
        Curtains
    </string>
    <string name="question6suggest_b_keyword">
        Monitor Position
    </string>
    <string name="question6suggest_c_keyword">
        Monitor Position
    </string>
    <string name="question7suggest_a_keyword">
        Paper Documents
    </string>
    <string name="question8suggest_a_keyword">
        Reflections
    </string>
    <string name="question9suggest_a_keyword">
        Vision Transitions
    </string>
    <string name="question9suggest_b_keyword">
        Vision Transitions
    </string>
    <string name="question9suggest_c_keyword">
        Vision Transitions
    </string>
    <string name="question10suggest_b_keyword">
        Light Flicker
    </string>
    <string name="glare_guidance">
        Glare is what happens when a bright light source or reflection interferes with how you are \'seeing\' an object. It can cause annoyance and discomfort, and can actually decrease a person\'s ability to see. To detect the possible glare using this function:\n\n
        1. Face the camera to the working visual area\n
        2. The possible glare will be marked instantaneously\n\n
        In addition:\n
        Use the botton at the bottom to capture the screen and save it.
    </string>
    <string name="info_important_head">Why is Lighting Important?</string>
    <string name="info_important_txt">Information about how lighting is related to working efficiency and health in both industrial and office settings.</string>
    <string name="info_different_head">What are Different Sources of Lights?</string>
    <string name="info_different_txt">Information about daylight and different types of artificial lighting and light fixtures.</string>
    <string name="info_flicker_head">What is Light Flicker?</string>
    <string name="info_flicker_txt">Information about what light flicker is, how it is caused, why it is a problem and how to deal with it.</string>
    <string name="info_glare_head">What is Glare?</string>
    <string name="info_glare_txt">Information about what glare is, how it is caused, why it is a problem and how to deal with it.</string>
    <string name="flicker_suggest">Some types of ballasts can reduce flicker considerably. Energy-efficient electronic ballasts take the 60 Hz supplied power and convert it to a much higher frequency (20,000 - 60,000 Hz). The resulting flicker frequency (twice the supplied power frequency, 40 -120 kHz) is so high that the human eye cannot detect any fluctuation in the light intensity – essentially flicker-free. An added benefit is that electronic ballasts produce less hum than that emitted by other kinds of ballasts.\n\n
        To Correct Flicker\n
        1. Replace bulbs on a scheduled basis. Old bulbs tend to flicker more and they are not as bright.\n
        2. Ensure that all parts of the light fixture, especially the ballast, are functioning properly.\n
        3. When replacements are needed, upgrade to fluorescent lighting that uses electronic ballasts.\n
        4. Discuss issues with your lighting manufacturer or supplier. Lighting technology can vary and options may be available.
    </string>
    <string name="light_correct_txt">
        <li>Replace bulbs on a regular schedule. Old bulbs give less light than new ones, so replace them before they burn out. Follow manufacturers\' instructions.</li> \n
        <li>Clean light fixtures regularly. Dirt on light fixtures reduces the amount of light given off. Light fixtures with open tops allow air currents to move dust up through the fixtures so dust and dirt do not accumulate on them.</li>\n
        <li>Add more light fixtures in appropriate places.</li> \n
        <li>Paint walls and ceilings light colours so light can be reflected.</li> \n
        <li>Use more reflected light and local lighting to eliminate shadows. For example, a covered light mounted under a transparent guard on a grinding wheel provides the added light needed to clearly see the task.</li> \n
        <li>Do not position the work station with the light fixture directly behind worker.</li>
    </string>
    <string name="flicker_view_suggest"><u>View Suggestions</u></string>
    <string name="read_more_light_level"><u>Read More About the Light Level</u></string>
    <string name="read_more_flicker"><u>Read More About the Flicker</u></string>
    <string name="read_more_glare"><u>Read More About the Glare</u></string>
    <string name="read_more_light_txt1">
        The amount of light we need varies and depends on\n
        <li>Type of task being done (such as demands for speed and accuracy).</li>\n
        <li>Type of surfaces (does it reflect or absorb light).</li>\n
        <li>General work area.</li>\n
        <li>Individual\'s vision.</li>\n\n
        The amount of light falling on a surface is measured in units called lux. Depending on the factors noted above, adequate general lighting is usually between 500 and 1000 lux* when measured 76 cm (30 inches) above the floor.\n
        * From: IESNA Lighting Handbook. 9th ed. Illuminating Engineering Society of North America, 2000. p. 10-13.\n\n
        To reach proper light levels and uniform light distribution in the visual environment, many light fixtures are designed to reflect light off walls, ceilings, and objects. The amount of light reflected off a surface can be measured. Suggestions for the percent of light reflected off surfaces in a typical office include:\n
        <li>Window blinds (40-50%).</li>\n
        <li>Walls (50% maximum).</li>\n
        <li>Business machines (50% maximum).</li>\n
        <li>Ceiling (70-80%).</li>\n
        <li>Floor (20-40%).</li>\n
        <li>Furniture (25-45%).</li>\n\n
        The percent value refers to the amount of light that a surface reflects relative to the amount that falls on the surface.\n
        In addition, light fixtures that are too widely spaced or wrongly positioned can create shadows. Objects between the light fixture and work being done can block the light and cast shadows. Likewise, workers sitting with their backs to windows, with light fixtures directly overhead or to the rear, cast shadows on their own work surfaces.
    </string>
    <string name="read_more_light_txt2">
        <li>Poor lighting can be a safety hazard – misjudgment of the position, shape, or speed of an object can lead to incidents and injury.</li>\n
        <li>Poor lighting can affect the quality of work, specifically in situations where precision is required, and overall productivity.</li>\n
        <li>Poor lighting can be a health hazard – too much or too little light strains eyes and may cause eye discomfort (burning, etc.) and headaches.</li>
    </string>
    <string name="read_more_glare_txt1">
        Glare is a common lighting problem. Glare is what happens when a bright light source or reflection interferes with how you are \'seeing\' an object. In most cases, your eyes will adapt to the brightest level of light. When this adaptation happens, it becomes harder to see the details in the duller or darker areas of the work space (even though they are actually sufficiently lit!). Glare can cause annoyance and discomfort, and can actually decrease a person\'s ability to see.
    </string>
    <string name="read_more_glare_txt2">
        <li>Light reflected from polished, shiny or glossy surfaces.</li>\n
        <li>Glass on picture frames, or windows at night.</li>\n
        <li>Monitors / screens.</li>
    </string>
    <string name="read_more_glare_txt3">
        <li>Very bright light from poorly positioned light fixtures.</li>\n
        <li>Sunlight.</li>
    </string>
    <string name="read_more_glare_txt4">
        <li>Using several small low-intensity light fixtures rather than one large high-intensity light fixture.</li>\n
        <li>Using light fixtures that diffuse or concentrate light well. Indirect light fixtures or direct light fixtures with parabolic louvres are two possibilities.</li>\n
        <li>Covering bare bulbs with louvers, lenses or other devices to control light.</li>\n
        <li>Increasing the brightness of the area around the glare source.</li>\n
        <li>Positioning light fixtures to reduce reflected light that is directed toward the eyes.</li>\n
        <li>Using low gloss paper or applying flat or semi-gloss paint and matte finishes on \'offending\' surfaces. Removing highly polished and shiny objects.</li>\n
        <li>Keeping general lighting levels at recommended levels.</li>
    </string>
</resources>