<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IllumiSmart</string>
    <string name="illumismart">IllumiSmart</string>
    <string name="self_assessment">Self-Assessment</string>
    <string name="home_selfassess">Evaluate the lighting condition of your workplace by answering a few questions.</string>
    <string name="measure_light_level">Measure Light Level</string>
    <string name="home_lightlevel">A quick tool to check whether your working area is too bright or too dark.</string>
    <string name="home_flicker">A quick tool to check whether there is flicker hazard.</string>
    <string name="detect_light_flicker">Detect Light Flicker</string>
    <string name="detect_glare">Detect Glare</string>z
    <string name="glare_event_true">Glare event: True</string>
    <string name="glare_event_false">Glare event: False</string>
    <string name="a_quick_tool_to_check_whether_there_is_glare_hazard">A quick tool to check whether there is glare hazard.</string>
    <string name="lightlevel_guidance">Light level is an important factor in the workplace. To measure the illuminance using this function:\n\n
        1. Push \t\t\t to start recording \n
        2. Face the light sensor up \n
        3. Moving the phone horizontally and slowly around the working area \n
        4. Push \t\t\t to pause recording \n\n
        In addition:\n
        \t\t : Reset the light meter \n
        \t\t : Save the measurement data</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance">Unsteady light may do harm to human and become safety hazards. To detect the possible flicker using this function: \n\n
        1. Face the light sensor direct to the light source \n
        2. Push \t\t\t to start detecting \n
        3. The Fluctuation Rate of the light source and whether it is a possible visible flicker will be displayed after 10 seconds \n\n
        In addition:\n
        \t\t : Reset the detector \n
        \t\t : Save the measurement data</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance_0">No flicker event detected.</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance_1to3">It seems this light source is a possible flicker.</string>
    <string name="flicker_guidance_3">It seems this light source is a certain visible flicker.</string>
    <string name="light_level_guidance_below">The average lighting level is below the guideline suggestions.</string>
    <string name="light_level_guidance_above">The average lighting level is above the guideline suggestions</string>
    <string name="light_level_guidance_among">The average lighting level follows the guidance.</string>
    <string name="light_level_view_details"><u>View Details</u></string>
    <string name="profile_below40_finework">According to your age and type of task being done, the recommended illuminance is:</string>
    <string name="light_level_below_suggest">If the measured average light level is under the guidance, view <u>Correction of Insufficient Light</u></string>
    <string name="light_level_above_suggest">If the measured average light level is above the guidance, it is suggested to conduct a glare test next.</string>
    <string name="occupation_question">Which of the following answers best describes your work type?</string>
    <string name="occupation_general_txt">Examples: Storeroom…</string>
    <string name="occupation_moderate_txt">Examples: Packing; despatch…</string>
    <string name="occupation_precise_txt">Examples: Simple assembly; locksmith’s work; winding thick wire onto spools; work on carpenter’s bench; milling…</string>
    <string name="occupation_fine_txt">Examples: Reading; writing; book-keeping; laboratory technician; assembly of fine equipment; woodworking by machine; fine work on toolmaking gig…</string>
    <string name="occupation_veryfine_txt">Examples: Technical drawing; colour proofing; adjusting and testing electrical equipement; assembling delicate electronics; watchmaking; invisible mending</string>
    <string name="age_question">What is your age?</string>
    <string name="question1_work">Do you work in the office or industry setting?</string>
    <string name="question_select_header">Choose one of the following</string>
    <string name="question2_discomfort">Are there any signs of frequent eye discomfort (e.g. eyestrain, blurred vision...) and/or headaches?</string>
    <string name="question_back_header">Back to the Previous Question</string>
    <string name="question3_sunlight">Does your workplace have access to the natural light (sunlight) via windows?</string>
    <string name="question4_curtains">Are there blinds or curtains on windows?</string>
    <string name="question5_computer">Do you have a computer in your working area and usually work with it?</string>
    <string name="question6_monitor_position">Which of the following answers best describes your desktop monitor position relative to the windows?</string>
    <string name="question6_a">Next to a window</string>
    <string name="question6_b">In front of a window</string>
    <string name="question6_c">Face to a window</string>
    <string name="question6_d">There is no window near my monitor</string>
    <string name="question7_paper">Do you sometimes feel it is difficult to view the paper documents on the desk?</string>
    <string name="question8_vision">Are there frequent transitions of vision between extremes of light and dark or near and far during working?</string>
    <string name="question9_lightbulb">When do you replace the light bulbs?</string>
    <string name="question9_a">When they stop working</string>
    <string name="question9_b">When the light is dimming or fluctuating</string>
    <string name="question9_c">On regular schedule</string>
    <string name="question10_clean">Do you usually clean light fixtures, upper walls, ceilings and task stations?</string>
    <string name="question10_a">Yes, on regular schedule or whenever needed</string>
    <string name="question10_b">Never</string>
</resources>